## **ROHIT JADAV**

TEAM LEAD – Cloud Security

rohitjadav@gmail.com



- B/402, Suyash Homes, Nr Vandemataram Township, New SG Road, Gota, Ahmedabad 382481
- in linkedin.com/in/rohit-jadav-6a02306a

## **SKILLS**

Problem solving Adaptability

Strong collaborative skills

Strong Work Ethic Time

Management

**Critical Thinking** 

**Handling Pressure** 

Leadership

## **LANGUAGES**

## **INERESTS & HOBBIES**

Drawing

**Painting** 

Travelling

Trekking

Music

# **RESUME OBJECTIVE**

IT Security Professional Services Manager with 9 years of experience in Information Security domain, looking for a challenging role in a reputable organization to utilize my technical, and management skills for the growth of the organization as well as to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the Information Security domain.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## TEAM LEAD - CLOUD SECURITY

Appsecco Limited, Bengaluru, India / December 2021 - Present

- Assess and reviews cloud network configurations from a security angle; as well as recommendations to fix any issues for AWS, Azure and Google Cloud
- Examine current cloud security practices and identify key risks, then report to address them
- Solve cloud-based security challenges using cloud native services, open-source tools and best practices
- Ensures adequate security solutions and controls are in place throughout Cloud platform, services, and solutions
- Guide the cloud security group, identifying opportunities for improvement and then driving those improvements through the enterprise
- Responsible for end-to-end delivery of the client-side testing and managing the deployed resources at National and International locations and make sure the projects are completed within the timeframe without compromising the quality of assessment

#### MANAGER - PROFESSIONAL SERVICES

Net Square Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad, India / April 2018 – November 21

- Manager information security projects, including planning and deployment of new processes and technologies.
- Developing and updating methodologies for Web, Network, Cloud, etc. security assessments
- Assessed security architecture and status of the network, desktop and mainframe systems and data through audits.
- Proactively identify technical and architectural risks, commenting and/or providing alternatives for improvement
- Responsible for end-to-end delivery of the client-side testing and managing the deployed resources at National and International locations and make sure the projects are completed within the timeframe without compromising the quality of assessment
- Strong track record in a consulting, relationship management, key account management

#### INFORMATION SECURITY ANALYST

Net Square Solutions Pvt. Ltd. / December 2015 - March 2018

## INFORMATION SECURITY ANALYST

Network Intelligence India Pvt. Ltd. / December 2013 – December 2015

# TRAINING & ENGAGEMENTS

#### **NULLCON GOA 2022**

Breaking and Pwning Apps and Servers on AWS and Google Cloud – Post Pandemic Edition (NULLCON 2022)

## **NSCONCLAVE 2020 (Internal)**

Advanced Wireless Reconnaissance and Testing (NSCONCLAVE2020)

# TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

#### CLOUD:

Prowler, CloudMapper, ScoutSuite, PMapper, Pacu, Steampipe

#### **NETWORK:**

Nmap, Metasploit, Nikto, Nessus, Wireshark, metasploit

#### DAST:

Burp Suite, OWASP ZAP, SQLMap, Astra

#### **MOBILE:**

MobSF, Drozer, Frida, APKTool, Objection, Jadx

#### **SOURCE CODE REVIEW:**

SonarQube, Find Security Bugs, FindBugs

#### **WIRELESS:**

Kismet, Aircrack-ng, TouchStone - RF Explorer

## **CERTIFICATION**

## AWS CERTIFIED SECURITY - SPECIALITY (Pursuing)

Amazon Web Services Training and Certification

#### AWS CERTIFIED SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT – ASSOCIATE

Amazon Web Services Training and Certification

## **CERTIFIED INFORMATION SECURITY CONSULTANT**

Institute of Information Security, Mumbai

## CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL HACKER (NxG)

Institute of Information Security, Mumbai

#### CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL FORENSICS ANALYST

Institute of Information Security, Mumbai

## **EDUCATION**

## BACHELOR of SCIENCE (INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY)

University of Mumbai 2013

## **TECHNICAL EXPERTISE**

## Cloud security

Container security (Kubernetes)

Security architecture review (Web/Mobile)

Web application & API security

Mobile application security

Network security

Source code review



hereby declare that the information given above is true to the
best of my knowledge

Place: Ahmedabad

Date:

Yours Faithfully,

Rohit Jadav